JOHN BRINK

STUDENT IN INTERACTIVE MEDIA TECHNOLOGY



CONTACT INFO

+46 70 65 250 88

🔽 j<u>ohn-brink@hotmail.com</u>

https://johnbrink.netlify.app

in John Brink

j<u>ohnbri</u>

COMPETENCES

UX Research	••••	React.js	••••
UI Prototyping	••••	Wordpress	••••
Figma	••••	Unity	••••
Adobe CC	••••	Python	••••
CSS/HTML	••••	C#	••••
Javascript	••••	Java	••••

LANGUAGES

Swedish
English
French

WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesperson

CIRCLE K, MÄRSTA AND HUDIKSVALL MAY 2017 – DEC 2017

- Retail salesperson at two stations.
- Served food, managed car rental services

Consultant

2COMPLETE, STOCKHOLM MAR 2019 - MAY 2019

- Seasonal work at a tire washing station.
- Organized, washed, and transported tires.

PROFILE

As a student in interactive media technology, I have developed skills for researching, developing, and evaluating digital applications with a focus on good user experiences. My current goal is to build my knowledge in product design to a professional level. People describe me as creative, open-minded, down-to-earth, responsible, and calm.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Exchange study program - Computer Science
CITY UNIVERSITY, HONGKONG
JAN 2022 - PRESENT (GRADUATING JUN 2022)

M.Sc. in Engineering - Interactive Media Technology
KTH ROYAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, STOCKHOLM
AUG 2018 - PRESENT (GRADUATING JUN 2023)

Summer course - Web Management LINNAEUS UNIVERSITY, VÄXJÖ JUN 2020 - AUG 2020

Upper Secondary School - Technology and Sustainability BROMANGYMANSIET, HUDIKSVALL AUG 2014 - JUN 2017

POSITIONS OF TRUST

Various positions

CHAPTER OF MEDIA TECHNOLOGY, STOCKHOLM AUG 2018 - SEP 2021

- Event manager of yearly ski trip in Åre.
- Event planner of Student Reception, twice.
- Art director of the communications board.
- Project manager of the career fair Medias Branschdag.
- Account manager of the career fair Medias Branschdag.